EKİNSU BOZDAĞ

Objective:

I am 26 years old. I graduated from Computer Science in 2019. I am currently working for a mobile game company. I have 2 years experience in hyper-casual mobile games. My ultimate aim is to try myself in various areas in mobile gaming and design the best for my future career.



EDUCATION

Bilkent University, Ankara

B.S. in Computer Engineering Department
Graduate in May 2019

Ankara Atatürk Lisesi, Ankara

EXPERIENCE

Kuixo,Inc., Ankara,CyberPark

Computer Engineer Intern (07/2018 - 08/2018)
Game Developing for mobile with Unity and C#

Creasaur Entertainment Co., Ankara, Cyber Park

Game Developer (11/2019 - 02/2020)
Game Developing for Hyper-Casual with Unity and C#

Lumos Games

Game Developer (07/2018 - 08/2018)
Game Developing for Hyper-Casual with Unity and C#

Address: Malazgirt Mahallesi. 930. Sokak. Buse Apartmanı. 7/3 Çankaya/Ankara (+90) 554 811 6061 <u>ekinzu09@gmail.com</u>

Skills

<u>Computer Skills:</u> Unity, C#,Git

<u>Personal Skills:</u> Creative, Motivated,

Sporty, Gamer

Interests

Fitness, Volleyball, Mobile Games, Board Games, Any Games, Yoga

Achievements

2019 CS Fair - Deeplay Marketing Award

Languages

Turkish(Native),

English(Advanced)

Social Activities

- High School Volleyball Team
- High School Festival
 Organization Committee
- Bilkent Volleyball Group